[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bob Newhart"]}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 10, "question": "Billy Ray Cyrus, probably the famous father on planet earth right now, Billy Ray how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 11, "answer": "I'm doing great, I just met Bob Newhart at the back.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Billy Ray Cyrus", "Billy Ray"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 12, "question": "Are you speaking with excitement about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 13, "answer": "Well, I'm telling you, starstruck.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 27, "question": "So what is your view of this huge Miley controversy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 28, "answer": "I'm a singer, songwriter, you know, first and foremost, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Miley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Did you know what she was going to do at the awards?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "I knew that she wanted to do something really special and something that everybody was going to be talking about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "POS", "WP", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "WP", "JJ", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 50, "question": "What do you say to those people who perhaps were huge fans of Hannah Montana and feel uncomfortable about the directions she's taking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 51, "answer": "Well that's what music is supposed to do is make you feel, you know, that's what music is supposed to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hannah Montana"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "Does she have any regrets about it or is she loving every second of the mayhem this caused?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "She has been so busy, like I mean every single night she's in the studio.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "As a dad?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 113, "question": "I mean, have I missed it all or she's pretty good as that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 114, "answer": "She's never been arrested you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "What is your response to those like that council and like people that have subscribed to it who have got serious concerns about what Miley did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "Well, I'm on the council, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Well they get very angry about things like Miley did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "They sure didn't (ph) too.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Miley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "You know the old saying, right, I mean you don't want me to say it do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "Yes, you can.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Do you think she'd be the biggest pop star in the world there, I mean she's been famous but this is a like a whole new level, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "It does seem like a whole new level and yes, she has been very famous but she has reason to a whole new level and it's -- I thought I'd seen it all until these last couple of weeks and the whole thing just kind of went to a whole new level.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 190, "question": "Did you think about your friend often?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 191, "answer": "Every single day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Did you question your faith at all in that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Because if you don't have that, you just have endless acrimony right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "What will you be singing for us?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "\"Hope is Just Ahead\".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Bill Donohue, let me ask you first of all, you're a pretty well- known hard line conservative on these matters, are you happy with the direction the Pope wants to take you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Yes, I'm delighted with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Donohue"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "RB", "PRP", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "Would you endorse every word of what he said about?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Well I -- Now I -- would I endorse it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "On abortion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "I tell you, people in all denominations, they are wondering -- they're wondering why this Pope is saying what he's saying, and they do see a sense of reform taking place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Is that what you're saying father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "I'm not coming back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "Is it big and heavy as it looks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "It's heavy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Is he dangerous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Actually, he's a genius.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Ed"]}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "Were there any names on the original acceptance speech that actually survived to the final moment when you want one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "I think I thanked Mr. Ed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bobby", "Bill Cosby", "Bill Cosby", "Jerry Seinfeld", "Jerry Seinfeld"]}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "PRP$", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RP", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "POS", "RB", ":", "IN", "POS", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 441, "question": "How did it make you feel mostly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 442, "answer": "Well, and first of all it's your peers, you know, its your peers who are saying --and I kind of, you know, I kind of said, well I'm just never going to get one, because when you come from a stand up comedy world it's like let's just --that's Bobby and Bob and that's Bill Cosby and me and Bill Cosby and that's Jerry Seinfeld, me and Jerry Seinfeld.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "But don't you want to hear about it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "All right, Bob.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Vermont"]}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "What is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "That I was an inn keeper in this craziest little town in Vermont.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "Your wife had that idea, right, for the finale scene?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "You're afraid of flying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "That's what I said.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Are you a fan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I think, as you said, a breath of fresh air.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Oh, really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "So, who do you find funny of the modern crop of comedians when you see them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "EWHART: Well, I like -- at first, it's not the modern crop anymore.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "Is there anybody under 90 you could put your finger on that makes you laugh other than Don Rickles?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "IN", "CD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "Well, I can put my finger on the mirror.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Don Rickles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky"]}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Do you like Ricky Gervais and Russell Brand and that style of British talent?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "I'm not -- I know Ricky.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Russell Brand"], "PERSON": ["Ricky Gervais"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130919pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "What about Ricky Gervais, when you see him (inaudible) people at the Emmy's, is that you find him funny?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Once I get the translation.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ricky Gervais"]}}]